{
    "id": "0277d72c3f40474e8f6a472eb1cb7aeb",
    "title": "Third Conditional Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If I had known her name, I ………………………… you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will tell",
                "would tell",
                "would have told"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "03b62a8f91d044d587a4c299fc4ad94a"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ……………………….. me, I would have told you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ask",
                "asked",
                "had asked"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "13e71e30ac9746b59a2384468d394520"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you hadn’t helped me, I …………………………… in real trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "would be",
                "would have been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ed93b88f27dd43729b85843882cb4f0c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He would have died if they ……………………………. him to hospital in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't take",
                "don't take",
                "hadn't taken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ea245f94bbbf42c5ae3ee622a87d3005"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane ……………………. if you had invited her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will come",
                "would come",
                "would have come"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "81d1486ebd824368bd20588c4f11369e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He would have helped you if you ………………………… more politely.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "request",
                "requested",
                "had requested"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "90ac1b50dac34301932d4c3a9d6bbac3"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had wanted to, I ………………………. anybody I like.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can marry",
                "could marry",
                "could have married"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fc72079208bf4eb2a500f654cc675f76"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he had run a bit faster, he …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can win",
                "could win",
                "could have won"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1a8d9fb68b9c40a38c0d7b603df83bcb"
        },
        {
            "question": "If my grandmother ………………………….. alive, she would have been 85 now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had been",
                "has been",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ae122cf6237c489aa1b1f1764743efd4"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ………………………… harder, you would have passed your exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "worked",
                "had worked"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a035a6ef3ba74cbaaa894987607db4bc"
        }
    ]
}